Edid, Maralyn Collection of National Partnership Council Papers 6265
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Maralyn Edid Collection of National Partnership Council Papers
1992-1999
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Edid, Maralyn
6265
0.5 cubic feet
0.5 linear ft.
Papers.
6308618
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, March 07, 2016
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, March 07, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6264: Maralyn Edid Collection of Xerox Corporation Labor-Management Relations Papers
Industrial relations; Employees -- Training of; Edid, Maralyn, 1950-; National Partnership Council (U.S.)
6308618
- National Partnership Council. Cornell University New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations (NYSSILR)., 1997 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  Workshops on Skills-Building for Partnership. Agenda.
- Defense Partnership Council Report, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Getting Results from Public Involvement., 1999 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Government That Works, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  AFGE Labor-Management Partnerships Making the Difference.
- National Partnership Council., 1996 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  A Report to the President on Progress in Labor-Management Partnerships.
- National Partnership Council Facilitation Project., 1997 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  Revised Work Plan.
- National Partnership Honorees., 1996 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Partnership Handbook. "A Roadmap to Partnership.", 1994 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Report. Preliminary Results of The National Partnership Council's 1997 Federal Sector Labor Relations Climate Survey. (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Training and Facilitation Handbook., 1996 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Twelve Myths of Partnership., 1997 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Union Strategy Guide for Labor-Management Participation Programs., 1992 (Box 1, Folder 12)